

## **EDUCATION**

#### **BACHELOR OF LAW**

Donetsk National University 2004-2008

#### LAW SPECIALIST

National Academy of Law 2009-2011

## **CURRENT STATUS**

## **ATTORNEY**

from 2011

### **ENTREPRENEUR**

from 2011

## OTHER INFORMATION

## LANGUAGE KNOWLEDGE:

- UKRAINIAN NATIVE
- RUSSIAN FLUENTLY
- ENGLISH UPPER-INTERMEDIATE

DRIVER'S LICENSE: A, A1, B
READY FOR BUSINESS TRIPS

#### **PHONE**

+38 050 189 90 28

#### **EMAIL**

YevdokymenkoDN@gmail.com

## **LOCATION** KYIV, UKRAINE

## YEVDOKYMENKO DENYS

LAWYER ATTORNEY GR-SPECIALIST

## **ABOUT ME**

I consider the interests of the client to be a priority in any case. Always focused on results. I quickly find contacts with colleagues, I have experience working in a team. I can make decisions quickly, I have an analytical mindset. Punctual, responsible and ready for challenging tasks.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## 2014-2022 DTEK LLC | CHIEF/LEADING LEGAL COUNSEL (7 years 11 months)

- performed GR-management in the directions of competition, tax, budget, land, environmental, etc. rights
- took part in project work to support priority projects
- took part in project work to support the procedure for obtaining and executing special permits for oil and gas facilities, carried out legal risk analysis, ensured the preparation of recommendations and comments
- took part in the support of M&A agreements

## 2011-2012 EASTERN LOGISTICS GROUP LLC | LEADING LEGAL COUNSEL

(8 months)

- provided legal support for current activities
- provided legal support for contractual and claim-lawsuit work
- provided representation of interests in judicial and executive authorities

### 2011-now PRIVATE ENTEPRENEUR, LAWYER

(more than 11 years)

- carried out legal analysis of cases, provided consultations on all areas of law
- provided legal support for clients' business processes
- interacted with state enterprises, participated in court hearings

# 2008-2011 ADMIN COURT | JUDGE'S ASSISTANT/BAILIFF (2 years 7 months)

- provided preliminary preparation of court cases for consideration - ensured the preparation of draft court decisions, requests, letters, and other materials related to the consideration of cases
- fulfilled the instructions of the presiding judge

### HARD SKILLS

- thorough knowledge in all areas of law (RADA.gov.ua, LIGA.net, etc
- analysis of court practice (COURT.gov.ua)
- analysis of legal entities (OpenDataBot, YouControl, state registers)
- application of common software for legal activities

### **SOFT SKILLS**

- communication
- teamwork
- patience
- time management